darveys.com 2019-08-13

# Privacy Policy

At Darveys, we follow a strictly adhered and comprehensive policy to protect the privacy of all our clients. We bear complete responsibility for the safeguarding of the personal information that you provide to us on our website. However, the company shall not be held liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosure of personal information by any third parties such as advertisers or other websites with access to our website. The privacy policies at Darveys are subject to change without prior notice.

**Personal Information for Darveys members are collected on the basis of the following criterion and categorization:**

## Profiling Information

This is the information provided by a consumer when registering as a member at Darveys.com. This includes Information about your personal identity such as gender, marital status, age, preferences, likes and dislikes etc.; financial information like banking details and any other information relating to your income or lifestyle; contact and shipping information like physical address, shipping address, postal address and contact numbers etc.; other information available for public use for social media like facebook, twitter etc.

## Payment & Account Information

Your account history with us including (without any limitation) all billing information and communications, payment history etc. are covered here. This information is maintained in encrypted form on secure servers.

## Service Usage

This refers to information pertaining to your preferences and navigation of our website, which is also kept private.

## Log Information

This refers to information such as web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request etc.

## Transactional Information

We also guard the information about your transactional history (other than banking details) of your e-commerce activities.

## Correspondence Information

This includes content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our services, along with email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, experts forum communications, fax mail communications and membership of mailing lists etc.

## User IDs

This includes usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you with regard to our services.

## Stored Information

Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc. shall be kept safe with us.

All information collected by us is meant for business purposes only. No part of this information shall be provided to any third parties or traded thereupon.

Disclosure of all personal information shall be in accordance with the privacy policy. If the details are required for any other purpose, then your prior written consent will be sought, failing the submission of which we shall not be able to continue to provide our services to you.

All information available on open, public platforms isn't covered by the Privacy Policy. The user shall bear the risk pertaining to sharing or disclosing any such information.

**All collection of personal information shall be done to:**

  * Be in accordance with the prevalent laws
  * Conduct business operations
  * Protect company systems
  * Enforce our rights
